<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on redmangoapple</title>
    <link>https://orangeappleak.github.io/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on redmangoapple</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 12:15:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://orangeappleak.github.io/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo&#39;s file Structure.</title>
      <link>https://orangeappleak.github.io/posts/hugofilestructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 12:15:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orangeappleak.github.io/posts/hugofilestructure/</guid>
      <description>Written By: karthik. The file structure of a hugo generated site. Hello there my code wizards, hope you enjoyed my first post and now lets move on to my second one (i need to stop counting my blog posts :/ ). So after reading my first post you might now be wondering what all the files in the root folder do and whats the actual use of them? Today we are just going to discuss that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why and how I created this blog??</title>
      <link>https://orangeappleak.github.io/posts/whyandhowicreatedthisblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 15:37:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orangeappleak.github.io/posts/whyandhowicreatedthisblog/</guid>
      <description>Written by: Karthik. Introduction First of all welcome to my fellow WIZARDS and thank you for taking your time to read this.
This being my first post in my blog, I will be taking a moment to discuss why I created this blog and how I did it.
I was thinking of creating a blog for a while now, but never actually did it until recently, there is this AWESOME cousin that I have(I&amp;rsquo;ll provide a link to his blog later in this post) and he had an awesome blog and some good posts, so I got inspired and thought why not create a blog and put some posts up, so that it will help me as well as other code wizards like YOU.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
